funfreepages.com 2004-06-07

# Privacy Policy for funfreepages.com

This is the web site of **Fun Free Pages (http://www.funfreepages.com, http://files.funfreepages.com)**. 

[Fun Free Pages](http://funfreepages.com/) is firmly committed to the privacy of our clients. We have created this Privacy Policy to let you know under what information is collected and how this information is used. If you have any questions regarding this policy, please click here to [contact us](mailto:webmaster@funfreepages.com).

1\. Personal Data. We retain the name and e-mail address of visitors who submit an e-card via our web site so that we may notify them if their e-card is chosen. This information is deleted at the end of each month.

2\. Confidentiality. No information of ANY kind is ever shared with third parties other than that which is clearly indicated herewithin.

3\. Aggregate Data. We gather certain generic information with respect to visitors' use of our web site such as the number of unique visitors and the areas on the web site that they favor. We only look at this data on a collective basis, in summary form.

4\. IP Addresses. We collect and analyze traffic on our web site by keeping track of the IP addresses of our visitors. An IP address is a unique number assigned to your computer when you are browsing the internet. We log this information so that we can monitor overall traffic trends as well as the number of visitors visiting the web site. This information is used SOLELY to improve the quality of our web site.

5\. Cookies. Cookies are pieces of information sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer's hard drive for record-keeping purposes. The web site analysis tool we use on our site employs the use of 'cookies' within our site. By tracking the information contained in the 'cookie', the software can calculate various aggregate statistical data. The cookie does not contain any personally identifiable information.

7\. External Links. On our site, we have links to other web sites that may collect personal information about you. This policy does not cover the information practices of such web sites. We encourage you to read the privacy policies of these sites as their policies may be very different.

8\. Unsolicted E-Mail. We do not send unsolicited e-mail messages to anyone. We will only send e-mail if one of our visitors has signed up for our free monthly newsletter, in response to a query, or if their e-card was chosen as one of the top e-cards of the month.

9\. If we make any material changes in our privacy practices, we will post a notice on our web site notifying users of the change. 

10\. Third Party Advertising. We use BUDS INC and other third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp).

11\. Third Party Cookies. In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser. 

Last updated January 22th, 2004

* * *

**In short:** I don't collect emails, I don't spam or cause trouble. Hit tracking scripts are installed so I can monitor traffic so I can see how popular the site is. That is all.
